<resources>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="app_name">Home Gardening</string>
    <string name="herb_heading">Herbs/Medicinal Plants</string>
    <string name="tulsi">Basil (Tulsi)</string>
    <string name="shrub_heading">Shrubs (Small thick plants)</string>
    <string name="climber_heading">Climbers</string>
    <string name="aloevera">Aloe vera</string>
    <string name="genda">Marigold (Genda)</string>
    <string name="methi">Fenugreek (Methi)</string>
    <string name="mint">Mint (Pudina)</string>
    <string name="ashwagandha">Ashwagandha</string>
    <string name="lemongrass">Lemon grass</string>
    <string name="khus">Khus</string>
    <string name="lavender">Lavender</string>
    <string name="parsley">Parsley (Ajamod)</string>
    <string name="coriander">Coriander (Dhania)</string>
    <string name="desc_tulsi" formatted="true">Tulsi also known as basil leaves, is a fairly common plant in
        Indian households. Considered holy by many religions, the tulsi plant is revered for
        its divine properties. When eaten, Basil provides us healthy doses of vitamins A, K,
        and C, as well as magnesium, iron, potassium, and calcium.</string>
    <string name="desc_tulsiTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b> Basil is a hardy plant that grows easily,
        indoors or out. It doesn\'t need much care and requires watering only every other day. </string>
    <string name="desc_tulsiGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 5 - 10 days</string>
    <string name="desc_tulsiBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b> \n\t\t - Cures fever
        \n\t\t - Beats diabetes \n\t\t - Protects the heart \n\t\t - Beats Stress
        \n\t\t - Dissolves kidney stones \n\t\t - Beats cancer \n\t\t - Keeps your skin and hair healthy and glowing
        \n\t\t - Cures headache</string>
    <string name="desc_aloevera">Aloe vera plants are common household plants which can grow in a
        variety of climates. Caring for an aloe vera plant is simple. This spiky green plant is very
        easy to grow indoors, and has countless healing properties and uses around the house.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_aloeveraTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Aloe vera needs well-drained, sandy potting soil.
        \n\t\t - Bright, sunny conditions are ideal, though aloe vera will put up with just a little sunlight
        \n\t\t - only watering about every two weeks or even less frequently, especially in the
        winter. Don’t water a little every day or so, or try to keep the soil moist, because
        you will rot out its roots.

    </string>
    <string name="desc_aloeveraGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 - 3 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_aloeveraBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Fighting cavities of Teeth and gums
        \n\t\t - Soothes Rashes and Skin Irritations
        \n\t\t - Treats Burns
        \n\t\t - Heals Cold Sores
        \n\t\t - Moisturizes Hair and Scalp
        \n\t\t - Treats Constipation
        \n\t\t - Helps with Digestion
        \n\t\t - Boosts the Immune System
        \n\t\t - Provides Antioxidants and Reduces Inflammation
        \n\t\t - Treats Diabetes
    </string>

    <string name="desc_genda">The Marigold, a cheerful and easy plant to grow, and the first choice
        among those who want a bright and splendid natural display for their homes! This annual plant
        flowers with radiant sprays of multi-colored brass, copper and gold flowers all throughout
        the summer season.</string>
    <string name="desc_gendaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
     Marigolds flower thrive in all zones. Due to their resilient nature, plant them almost anywhere
        and they will start growing. For the best results, plant marigolds in places where they get
        plenty of heat and sunlight.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_gendaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 5 - 10 days</string>
    <string name="desc_gendaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Arrests Inflammation
        \n\t\t - Treats Acne
        \n\t\t - Fights A Fever
        \n\t\t - Stops Bleeding In Gums
        \n\t\t - Protects Your Eyes, Treats Conjunctivitis
        \n\t\t - Tackles Fungal Infections
        \n\t\t - Aids Wound Healing And Repairs Tissue
        \n\t\t - Treats Dermatitis, Burns, And Inflammatory Skin Conditions
        \n\t\t - Stops Hemorrhoid Bleeding
        \n\t\t - Eases Cramps And Digestive Problems
        \n\t\t - Treats Ear Pain

    </string>

    <string name="desc_methi">Fenugreek or methi leaves are pungent and aromatic. They are great for
        health and have been traditionally used as a spice as well as medicine in the Indian subcontinent,
        the Middle East and northern Africa. You can use the leaves dried or fresh, seeds ground or
        whole as a flavor to any menu.</string>
    <string name="desc_methiTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Methi prefers neutral soil with at least 4 hours of sun and shade in afternoon. Requires
        regular watering.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_methiGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2-4 days</string>
    <string name="desc_methiBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Improves Digestive Problems and Cholesterol Levels
        \n\t\t - Reduces Inflammation Inside the Body
        \n\t\t - Promotes Milk Flow in Breastfeeding
        \n\t\t - Lowers Inflammation from Outside the Body
        \n\t\t - Adds Flavor and Spice to Food
        \n\t\t - Helps with Eating Disorders
        \n\t\t - Improves Exercise Performance
    </string>

    <string name="desc_mint">Mint plants are sturdy perennial herb plants that are extremely easy to
        grow in full sun or part shade. Mints work well in any garden setting. Mint plants can also
        be a wonderful ornamental plant; lovely foliage, some flowers and that incredible aroma
        makes mint a essential herb plant for any garden.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_mintTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        All mints prefer a cool, moist spot in partial shade but will also grow in full sun. One
        plant of each cultivar you select will soon provide more than enough mint for home use.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_mintGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 10 - 15 days</string>
    <string name="desc_mintBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Aids in Digestion
        \n\t\t - Treats Nausea and Headache
        \n\t\t - Prevents Respiratory Disorders
        \n\t\t - Treats Asthma
        \n\t\t - Aids in Breast Feeding
        \n\t\t - Reduces Depression and Fatigue
        \n\t\t - Skin Care
        \n\t\t - Prevents Memory Loss
        \n\t\t - Weight Loss
        \n\t\t - Improves Sterility
        \n\t\t - Oral Care
        \n\t\t - Cures Allergies and Hay Fever
        \n\t\t - Prevents Cancer
    </string>

    <string name="desc_ashwagandha">Ashwagandha has become one of the most popular Ayurvedic herbs
        in the Western world. By providing a nourishing, yet energizing effect, ashwagandha can
        support a healthy nervous system. With the use of ashwagandha, stress doesn’t impact the
        nervous system with such intensity.</string>
    <string name="desc_ashwagandhaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Grows in dry and sunny location.
        \n\t\t - needs sandy and well-draining soil.
        \n\t\t - Needs less water.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_ashwagandhaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_ashwagandhaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - It\'s an Ancient Medicinal Herb
        \n\t\t - Can Reduce Blood Sugar Levels
        \n\t\t - Has Anti-Cancer Properties
        \n\t\t - Can Reduce Cortisol Levels
        \n\t\t - Reduce Stress and Anxiety
        \n\t\t - Reduce Symptoms of Depression
        \n\t\t - Can Boost Testosterone and Increase Fertility in Men
        \n\t\t - Increase Muscle Mass and Strength
        \n\t\t - Reduce Inflammation
        \n\t\t - Lower Cholesterol 
        \n\t\t - May Improve Brain Function, Including Memory
    </string>

    <string name="desc_lemongrass">The Lemongrass plant grows largely in clumps. It has long, thin,
        flat greenish-grey tinged reeds. It has exquisite fresh, lemony fragrance that intensifies
        when you crush or stroke the leaves.</string>
    <string name="desc_lemongrassTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Grow in a pot or container in a sunny spot indoors. Grows quickly.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lemongrassGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 5 to 21 days</string>
    <string name="desc_lemongrassBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Helps Digestion
        \n\t\t - Controls Cholesterol Levels
        \n\t\t - Cleanses and Detoxifies
        \n\t\t - Heals Colds and Flu
        \n\t\t - Fights Cancer
        \n\t\t - Reduces Arthritis Pain
    </string>

    <string name="desc_khus">khus (Vetiver) plant is aromatic and has a characteristic fragrance.
        It has long, thin and rigid leaves. The roots are spongy, branched and most important part
        used as medicine.</string>
    <string name="desc_khusTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        requires well-drained soil and full sun.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_khusGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> a</string>
    <string name="desc_khusBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Utilized for perfumes, aromatherapy, cosmetic, creams, herbal skin care as well as
        soaps used in a Ayurveda.
        \n\t\t - Treats sores and acne
        \n\t\t - Khus roots can improve red blood cells deficiency
        \n\t\t - Treats poor blood circulation
        \n\t\t - Treats dry skin, cracked and brittle skin, wounds, cuts.
        \n\t\t - Cures arthritis as well as muscular aches and pains.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lavender">Lavender is one of the most popular flowering herbs. Easy to grow,
        lavender is loved for its beautiful flowers and wonderful aroma. All you need is to grow and
        maintain this fragrant flowering herb is a suitable spot in the garden.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lavenderTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Lavender seeds are slow to germinate. This plant thrives best under warm, sunny conditions
        in well-drained soil.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lavenderGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 3 - 4 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_lavenderBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Reduces Anxiety and Stress
        \n\t\t - Treats Sleep Issues
        \n\t\t - Skin Care
        \n\t\t - Antiseptic Ability
        \n\t\t - Hair Care
        \n\t\t - Protects Heart Health
    </string>

    <string name="desc_parsley">Parsley is a plant with bright green, feather-like leaves. This
        popular herb is used in sauces, salads, and especially soups, as it lessens the need for salt.
        Not only is parsley the perfect garnish, it’s also good for you; it’s rich in iron and
        vitamins A and C.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_parsleyTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Parsley needs moist, well-turned soil. It does well in both full-sun and part-sun
        environments and needs less water.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_parsleyGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 10 - 25 days</string>
    <string name="desc_parsleyBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Controls Diabetes
        \n\t\t - Controls Arthritis
        \n\t\t - Treats toothaches, bruises, insect bites, and rough skin.
        \n\t\t - Controls kidney stones, urinary tract infections, and gallbladder stones.
        \n\t\t - Strengthens the Immune System
    </string>
    <string name="desc_coriander">Coriander is a highly aromatic herb that is used to enhance the
        flavor of many South-East Asian and Mexican cuisines. All parts of the plant are edible,
        but the fresh leaves and the dried seeds are the parts most traditionally used in cooking.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_corianderTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Coriander requires temparate climate. It doesn\'t survive in frosty conditions or even in extreme heat.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_corianderGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 - 3 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_corianderBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Lower Blood Sugar
        \n\t\t - Ease Digestive Discomfort
        \n\t\t - Decrease Blood Pressure
        \n\t\t - Fight Food Poisoning
        \n\t\t - Improve Cholesterol Levels
        \n\t\t - Help Urinary Tract Infections
        \n\t\t - Support Healthy Menstrual Function
        \n\t\t - May Prevent Neurological Inflammation and Disease
    </string>
    <string name="rose">Rose (Gulab)</string>
    <string name="hibisbus">Hibiscus (Jaswand)</string>
    <string name="jasmine">Jasmine (Chameli)</string>
    <string name="bougainvillea">Bougainvillea</string>
    <string name="nerium_oleander">Nerium Oleander</string>
    <string name="fern">Fern</string>
    <string name="arecapalm">Areca Palm</string>
    <string name="dracaena">Dracaena</string>
    <string name="azalea">Azalea</string>
    <string name="dahlia">Dahlia</string>
    <string name="lily">Lily</string>
    <string name="orchid">Orchid</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="about_heading">About Home Gardening</string>
    <string name="about_app">Home Gardening is an app which provides information about the plants
        that you can easily plant at home and will make your home decorative and look beautiful. It
        also provides you information about the necessary care and requirements for the various plants,
        their germination time and benefits.
    </string>
    <string name="about_footer">HAPPY GARDENING !!!</string>
    <string name="blue_morning_glory">Blue morning glory</string>
    <string name="moneyplant">Money Plant</string>
    <string name="star_jasmine">Star Jasmine</string>
    <string name="flame_vine">Flame Vine</string>
    <string name="butterfly_pea">Butterfly Pea</string>
    <string name="tomatoes">Tomatoes</string>
    <string name="loofah">Loofah</string>
    <string name="desc_rose">Roses are one of the most beautiful, traditional, and fragrant flowers
        that you can plant in your garden. "Every rose has its thorn," but these gorgeous flowers
        don't actually require a lot of care. All they really need is some attention and a sunny spot
        with good drainage.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_roseTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - The most appropriate time to plant the roses is during autumn or during spring.
        \n\t\t - Use a soil mixture that is rich in nutrients and slightly permeable
        \n\t\t - If you have noticed that the soil dries out very quickly you may have to water your rose plant every day.
        \n\t\t - For healthy rose plant you should place them near a south-facing window with good ventilation
    </string>

    <string name="desc_roseGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> About 6 - weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_roseBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
    \n\t\t 1. Health Benifit
    \n\t\t - Enriched With Vital Vitamins
    \n\t\t - Fights Depression
    \n\t\t - Effective Against Heart Problems and HIV
    \n\t\t - Rose Oil Has Multiple Benefits
    \n\t\t - Rose Tea Cures Infections
    \n\t\t - Rose Water Relieves Constipation
    \n\t\t 2. Beauty Benefits-
    \n\t\t - Antibacterial
    \n\t\t - Anti-inflammatory
    \n\t\t - Antioxidants
    \n\t\t - Moisturizing
    \n\t\t - Naturally fragrant
    \n\t\t - Relaxing
    \n\t\t - Toning
    </string>
    <string name="desc_hibiscus">Hibiscus are large shrubs or small trees that produce huge, colorful,
        trumpet-shaped flowers over a long season. They have dark green leaves and can grow to 15 feet
        tall in frost-free areas. Flowers may be up to 6 inches diameter, with colors ranging from yellow
        to peach to red.They are generally divided into four groups: Hardy Hibiscus, Rose of Sharon,
        Tropical Hibiscus, and all the various species of Hibiscus.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_hibiscusTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Select a site  Hibiscus require full sun and well-drained soil and also adapt well to growing
        in containers. Hibiscus require at least 1 inch of rain (or equivalent watering) each week.
        They like to be constantly moist, but not wet.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_hibiscusGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 1 to 4 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_hibiscusBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t 1. Health Benifits -
        \n\t\t - Relief from high blood pressure and high cholesterol,
        as well as digestive, immune system, and inflammatory problems.
        \n\t\t - Cure liver disease
        \n\t\t - Reduces the risk of cancer.
        \n\t\t - Speed up the metabolism and help in healthy, gradual weight loss.
        \n
        \n\t\t - 2. Beauty Benefits-
        \n\t\t - Rich in Antioxidants. Antioxidants are amazing for your skin's health.
        \n\t\t - Natural Shampoo
        \n\t\t - Evens Skin Tone
        \n\t\t - Intense Moisturizing Action
        \n\t\t - Encourages Hair Growth
        \n\t\t - Exfoliates Dead Cells
        \n\t\t - Delays Premature Graying of Hair
    </string>

    <string name="desc_jasmine">Jasmine is a genus of shrubs and vines in the olive family. It is a
        sweet smelling plant that is renowned for its ornamental beauty and distinctive fragrance.
        Jasmine has small white flowers, although some species have bright yellow, with long shoots
        that climb. Typically, each flower will have about four to nine petals, two locules, and one
        to four ovules, with two stamens and very short filaments.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_jasmineTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Choose a warm, sheltered location when growing jasmine. All jasmine plants prefer sun to light
        shade sites with well-draining and moderately fertile soil. Install the plant in the ground at
        the same level it was growing in the nursery pot.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_jasmineGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> About 6 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_jasmineBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Boosts Immunity and Fights Fever
        \n\t\t - Jasmine Tea Treats Stress
        \n\t\t - Cures Oral Problems
        \n\t\t - Heals Injuries
        \n\t\t - Good For Cardiovascular Health
    </string>

    <string name="desc_fern">A fern is a member of a group of vascular plants that reproduce via spores
        and have neither seeds nor flowers. Fern stems are often referred to as rhizomes, even though
        they grow underground only in some of the species. Leaves are divided into two types a trophophyll
        and a sporophyll.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_fernTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Just dig a hole that is more or less the same size of the fern pot and plant the fern in the
        hole so that the plant sits just above (approximately 1 to 2 inches) level. Ensure that the
        soil has good amount of moisture content but continually damp or wet.
     </string>
    <string name="desc_fernGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 - 6 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_fernBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Used for Rheumatism
        \n\t\t - Used for Lungs
        \n\t\t - Used for Gynecology (including menstrual, postpartum, and breastfeeding)
        \n\t\t - Used for the Blood
        \n\t\t - Used for Digestion (including stomach ache and parasites)
    </string>

    <string name="desc_palm">The Areca Palm is a lovely tree that has gorgeous long, feathery fronds
        with golden stems that arch over towards the top. They are moderate growers, maturing to a height
        of 25-30 feet tall and 8-10 feet in width. The Areca Palm is the top choices for an indoor palm.
        It does not develop a single, upright trunk, but instead grows as a clump with numerous short
        stems at the base, and upright fronds, growing to 6 feet tall.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_palmTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Allow the top 1-2” of soil to dry out before watering an Areca Palm. Never allow an Areca to
        sit in water as this causes root rot. It requires bright indirect light.
     </string>
    <string name="desc_palmGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 - 6 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_palmBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Most efficient air purifying plant
        \n\t\t - Releases copious amounts of moisture into the air
        \n\t\t - the areca is consistently rated among the best houseplants for removing all indoor air toxins tested
    </string>

    <string name="desc_dracaena">Dracaena fragrans is a slow growing shrub,usually multistemmed at the base.
        They compose of a large group of popular foliage plants. Most grow strongly upright with long,
        straplike leaves variegated with white, cream, or red. Dracaenas grow well at average room temperatures
        but don't like cold drafts. Give plants medium to bright light to maintain best leaf color.
        Allow the soil to dry to the touch between waterings.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_dracaenaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Dracaena require shed leaves in order to grow new ones. These plants are sensitive to fluoride,
        which can be found in tap water,  so it's essential to use purified water when caring for this plant.
     </string>
    <string name="desc_dracaenaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> About 30 to 40 days</string>
    <string name="desc_dracaenaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Ornamental benefits
        \n\t\t - Air purification
        \n\t\t - Humidity control
    </string>

    <string name="desc_azalea">Azaleas are flowering shrubs making up part of the genus Rhododendron.
        Prefers moist well drained soil in semi-shade. Water well during Summer. Mass plant to create
        a stunning display. Lovely in decorative tubs and containers. Evergreen early flowering azalea
        bearing double red flowers.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_azaleaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Azaleas shrubs should be planted in the spring, preferably within cool, lightly shaded sites.
        They have shallow roots and require a well-drained, acidic soil.
     </string>
    <string name="desc_azaleaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 10 days to 3 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_azaleaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Combat formaldehyde from sources such as plywood or foam insulation.
        \n\t\t - Improve indoor air quality in your home or work space
    </string>

    <string name="desc_dahlia">Dahlias are annual blooming plants, with mostly tuberous roots. While
        some have herbaceous stems, others have stems which lignify in the absence of secondary tissue
        and resprout following winter dormancy, allowing further seasons of growth. Each floret is a
        flower in its own right, but is often incorrectly described as a petal, particularly by horticulturists.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_dahliaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Grows from seed or from tubers. Plant in rich soil; offer morning sun and protection from wind.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_dahliaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 10 to 14 days</string>
    <string name="desc_dahliaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Dahlia flowers can be used as a medicine
        \n\t\t - Dahlia flowers can be used as a food preservative
        \n\t\t - Used for decoration
    </string>

    <string name="desc_lily">A useful shrub for shady parts of the garden, pieris is often grown
        under taller broad-leafed evergreen trees. Most striking when it is adorned with white, pink,
        or nearly red flowers in late winter to early spring, it stays attractive throughout the year
        thanks to its glossy dark green foliage. Since it is taller than it is wide (to an eventual
        9 by 6 feet), it’s a suitable choice for somewhat narrow spaces.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lilyTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Light: Full sun or partial shade; protect from afternoon sun.
        \n\t\t - Soil: Moist, well-drained soil; cannot tolerate wet soil.
        \n\t\t - Watering: The key to getting your new shrub or tree off to a good start is moisture.
        \n\t\t - Fertilizer: We recommend against fertilizing at planting time and during the first growing season in your garden.
        \n\t\t - Continuing Care: Shelter from wind and afternoon sun, which can encourage their susceptibility to lace bug.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_lilyGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>   2 to 6 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_lilyBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Reduces Scars
        \n\t\t - Lightens Skin Tone
        \n\t\t - Heart Diseases:
        \n\t\t - Mental Problems:
        \n\t\t - Treatment Of Chronic Lung Diseases:
        \n\t\t - Treatment Of Urinary Tract Infection:
        \n\t\t - Keep Digestion Healthy:
        \n\t\t - Breaks down kidney stones.
        \n\t\t - Prevents water retention in the body.
        \n\t\t - Reduces pain associated with joint problems like gout and rheumatism.
        \n\t\t - Treats conjunctivitis.
        \n\t\t - Essential oil is used to treat paralysis, shock, and speech loss.
        \n\t\t - Helps to treat leprosy and swelling.
        \n\t\t - Treats poisoning and alcoholism by causing vomiting.
     </string>

    <string name="desc_orchid">Orchids are easily distinguished from other plants, as they share some
        very evident, shared derived characteristics, or "apomorphies". Among these are: bilateral
        symmetry of the flower (zygomorphism), many resupinate flowers, a nearly always highly modified
        petal (labellum), fused stamens and carpels, and extremely small seeds.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_orchidTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Requires proper light Exposure Right. orchids should be watered once a week.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_orchidGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 1 to 9 months</string>
    <string name="desc_orchidBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Cures Stomach Ulcer
        \n\t\t - Cures Menstrual Problems
        \n\t\t - For Loss Weight
        \n\t\t - Remedy For Indigestion
        \n\t\t - Cures Thyroid Problems
        \n\t\t - Cures Urinary Tract Infection
        \n\t\t - Quick Relief Constipation
        \n\t\t - Cures Respiratory Problems
        \n\t\t - Stimulates The Cell Activity
        \n\t\t - Improves Overall Health
    </string>

    <string name="desc_oleander">Nerium oleander, commonly known as oleander, is a highly toxic
        ornamental shrub that has been cultivated since ancient times. An evergreen shrub (or small
        tree) that grows to approximately 6 m with thick, gummy, clear sap; leaves opposite or whorled,
        simple, leathery, with smooth margins and conspicuous pinnate veins; flowers clustered at tip
        of twigs, 5-parted, funnel-shaped, white, pink, red, or yellow.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_oleanderTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        If the soil is poor, feed the plant lightly with a balanced fertilizer during its first spring.
        Once established, oleander shrubs don\'t require routine fertilization.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_oleanderGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>Aprox. 1 months</string>
    <string name="desc_oleanderBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Helping with muscle cramps.
        \n\t\t - Natural support for asthma, epilepsy and paralysis.
        \n\t\t - Help for skin conditions such as eczema.
        \n\t\t - Powerful all natural organic insecticide.
        \n\t\t - Usefulness in aiding heart conditions.
        \n\t\t - Natural support for healthy blood sugar levels
        \n\t\t - Possible support for the HIV virus
        \n\t\t - Usefulness in increasing healing times for wounds, when crushed and applied topically
        \n\t\t - Powerful immune-system stimulator
        \n\t\t - Promoting normal menstrual cycles
        \n\t\t - Aiding the body in the fight against arthritis, psoriasis &amp; hepatitis C
    </string>

    <string name="desc_bougainvillea">Bougainvillea grows as a woody vine or climber, reaching 15 to 40
        feet with heart-shaped leaves and thorny stems. The flowers are generally small, white, and
        highlighted by several brightly colored modified leaves called bracts. The bracts can vary
        in color, ranging from white, red, mauve, purple-red, or orange. Its fruit is a small,
        inconspicuous, dry, elongated achene.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_bougainvilleaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        To grow bougainvillea, plant it in full sun, slightly acidic and well-drained soil, and a
        relatively hot and dry climate.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_bougainvilleaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>Aprox. 1 month</string>
    <string name="desc_bougainvilleaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Bougainvillea leaves are used to cure variety of disorders like for diarrhea, and to reduce stomach acidity.
        \n\t\t - It is used for cough and sore throat.
        \n\t\t - Infusion of flowers used as treatment for low blood pressure..
        \n\t\t - Leaves are use to cure diabetes 2.
        \n\t\t - Stems help in hepatitis.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_butterflypea">Butterfly pea is a perennial vine up to three feet long, but it
        is a twining vine and not a climbing vine so look for this one growing along the ground.
        Like many plants in the Pea family it has trifoliate leaves. These compound leaves are alternate,
        stalked, and have three leaflets over an inch long,with the terminal leaflet on a long stalk.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_butterflypeaTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Butterfly pea flowers grow in nearly any type of soil, including nutrient-poor, but sandy,
        acidic soil is preferable. Water the plant regularly during the first growing season, but
        beware of overwatering.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_butterflypeaGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 to 3 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_butterflypeaBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Improve eyesight
        \n\t\t - Improve hair growth
        \n\t\t - Improve skin
        \n\t\t - Aphrodisiac
        \n\t\t - Antioxidant
        \n\t\t - Anti-inflammatory
        \n\t\t - Anti-Asthmatic
        \n\t\t - Anti-diabetic
        \n\t\t - Anti-cancer and anti-tumor
        \n\t\t - Anti-anxiety and depression
    </string>

    <string name="desc_flame_vine">Butterfly pea is a perennial vine up to three feet long, but it
        is a twining vine and not a climbing vine so look for this one growing along the ground.
        Like many plants in the Pea family it has trifoliate leaves. These compound leaves are alternate,
        stalked, and have three leaflets over an inch long,with the terminal leaflet on a long stalk.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_flame_vineTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Butterfly pea flowers grow in nearly any type of soil, including nutrient-poor, but sandy,
        acidic soil is preferable. Water the plant regularly during the first growing season, but
        beware of overwatering.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_flame_vineGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 2 to 3 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_flame_vineBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Improve eyesight
        \n\t\t - Improve hair growth
        \n\t\t - Improve skin
        \n\t\t - Aphrodisiac
        \n\t\t - Antioxidant
        \n\t\t - Anti-inflammatory
        \n\t\t - Anti-Asthmatic
        \n\t\t - Anti-diabetic
        \n\t\t - Anti-cancer and anti-tumor
        \n\t\t - Anti-anxiety and depression
    </string>

    <string name="desc_loofah">Loofah is a genus of tropical and subtropical vines in the cucumber
        family. Loofah, (genus Luffa), also spelled luffa, also called vegetable sponge, sponge gourd,
        or rag gourd, genus of seven species of annual climbing vines of the gourd family,native to
        the Old World tropics.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_loofahTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Loofah yields well in warm climates. It can be grown on any good soil. The plant requires
        only little water but regular watering is essential.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_loofahGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>  7 to 14 days</string>
    <string name="desc_loofahBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Reduce arthritis
        \n\t\t - Prevents eye ailments
        \n\t\t - Cardiovascular benefits
        \n\t\t - Prevent diabetes
        \n\t\t - Prevents muscle pain
        \n\t\t - Reduce arthritis
        \n\t\t - Treat Anemia
        \n\t\t - Skin health
        \n\t\t - Migraine headaches
    </string>

    <string name="desc_moneyplant">Money plant is a popular houseplant that is grown indoors mostly
        in water. The plant is called a money plant because its leaves (round, flat, heart-shaped,
        dark green, and plump) resemble coins. It is a perennial and may be grown as either a trailer
        or a climber. Young plants bear three- to four-inch-long heart-shaped leaves. This plant is
        grown mainly indoors. Money plant also used by many people for there fortune and good luck.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_moneyplantTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Money plant should be grown where there is less sunlight or in shade. Do not water them
        every time, let the soil dry and then water.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_moneyplantGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> 5–6 months</string>
    <string name="desc_moneyplantBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Money plant as one of the best plants to purify air polluted with synthetic chemicals
        from furniture and cleaning solutions.
        \n\t\t - It energizes the home by filtering air and increasing oxygen inflow.
        \n\t\t - Placing a money plant in front of a sharp corner or angle reduces anxiety and stress.
        \n\t\t - It also helps avoid arguments and sleep disorders.
        \n\t\t - Money plants activate positive energy in our day-to-day lives.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_morningGlory">Morning glories are annual climbers with slender stems, heart-shaped
        leaves, and trumpet-shaped flowers of pink, purple-blue, magenta, or white. They have a beautiful
        shape before they unfold in the sun and romantic tendrils that lend old-fashioned charm. The
        flowers bloom from early summer to the first frost. Their big, fragrant, colorful flowers
        attract butterflies and hummingbirds.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_morningGloryTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Grow annuals in a sunny, sheltered site. They need a lot of sun and moderately fertile, well-drained soil.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_morningGloryGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>  5 to 21 days</string>
    <string name="desc_morningGloryBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Reduced stress and increased sense of well-being
        \n\t\t - Improve air quality
        \n\t\t - Reduce background noise
        \n\t\t - This has been used medicinally in the treatment of various mental disorders.
        \n\t\t - Morning glory is believed to have antibacterial and antifungal properties too
        \n\t\t - preventing the onset of various diseases as salmonella poisoning
    </string>

    <string name="desc_starJasmine">Jasmine is a genus of shrubs and vines in the olive family. It is a
        sweet smelling plant that is renowned for its ornamental beauty and distinctive fragrance.
        Jasmine has small white flowers, although some species have bright yellow, with long shoots
        that climb. Typically, each flower will have about four to nine petals, two locules, and one
        to four ovules, with two stamens and very short filaments.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_starJasmineTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Choose a warm, sheltered location when growing jasmine. All jasmine plants prefer sun to light
        shade sites with well-draining and moderately fertile soil. Install the plant in the ground at
        the same level it was growing in the nursery pot.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_starJasmineGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b> About 6 weeks</string>
    <string name="desc_starJasmineBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Boosts Immunity and Fights Fever
        \n\t\t - Jasmine Tea Treats Stress
        \n\t\t - Cures Oral Problems
        \n\t\t - Heals Injuries
        \n\t\t - Good For Cardiovascular Health
    </string>

    <string name="desc_tomatoes">The tomato is the edible, often red plant. The Tomato plant has
        soft and hairy stems. It has 5-9 leaflets and the leaves can be 4 to 24 inches long. The
        flowers on the tomato plant are small, yellow and have five pointed lobes on the corolla.
        When the actual fruit is unripe it is green and when it does ripen it is deep red with most varieties.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_tomatoesTip1"><b><i>Growing Tip: </i></b>
        Plant in fertile soil, amended with compost, mulch and provide even moisture. Plant deeper
        than they were growing in the containers as it makes a stronger roots system.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_tomatoesGerm"><b><i>Germination: </i></b>5 to 10 days</string>
    <string name="desc_tomatoesBenefits"><b><i>Benefits: </i></b>
        \n\t\t - Improves vision
        \n\t\t - Helps fight cancer
        \n\t\t - Maintaining blood health
        \n\t\t - Reduces risk of heart disease
        \n\t\t - Good for digestion
        \n\t\t - Protect the Heart
        \n\t\t - Lower Hypertension
        \n\t\t - Skin Care
        \n\t\t - Prevent Urinary Tract Infections
        \n\t\t - Manage Diabetes
    </string>

</resources>
